The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
This fog
seems thicker than last time.
Something's wrong...
This place is dangerous.
If you refuse to return to the God Slaying Chariot in my bag of holding,
I'll be more dangerous for the both of us.
I saw in the Ancient God's memories,
that the Moongazer Serpent has 3 forms.
The first is the dormant form
with no offensive power.
The second is when the tentacles are withdrawn
and the Moongazer Serpent will change into various shapes.
The third
is the most dangerous assault form.
All the tentacles will be extended
and attack all living beings within its sight.
That tentacle just now
is quite similar
to this third form.
1000 zhang long...
Note: 1 zhang = 3m
This Moongazer Serpent hasn't fully awakened yet,
it's still transitioning to the third form.
Could it be that within these 100 years,
someone has come here ?
I saw in the memory inheritance
what the sensitive spot of a Moongazer Serpent is.
To anesthetize this enormous Moongazer Serpent,
I must use the Celestial Ascension Fruits at the base of the tentacles.
The effect of the Celestial Ascension Fruits probably won't last long.
I must be fast.
Refine !
The first Celestial Ascension Fruits are set.
I just need
to do the same everywhere.
3 hours later
I placed Celestial Ascension Fruits
on about 80% of the Moongazer Serpent's tentacles.
When I extract the bone,
I'll trigger all of the restrictions at once
to anesthetize it.
Before extracting the bone,
I need to confirm one last thing.
Celestial spiritual energy ?
Looks like someone really did come here.
No wonder the Moongazer Serpent awakened.
The pain caused by this injury
is enough to enrage it.
The person who broke this bone
obviously didn't recognize the Moongazer Serpent.
Otherwise, they would never have dared to do this.
Greed !?
They really did come after me !
I just don't know if those old monsters came together
or if Greed is all alone.
I've already lost the Seven Stars Sword Formation
so I can't leave this mountain here.
Stop !
This Moongazer Serpent is already in its third form...
If he just stabbed his mountain artifact,
it wouldn't be like this.
Could it be...
Inside the Moongazer Serpent,
there is an extremely poisonous item
called the Moonflower.
Only the blood of an Ancient God can neutralize it.
If anything endangers the Moonflower,
it will enrage the Moongazer Serpent.
After the Moongazer Serpent dies,
the Moonflower will cause its corpse to self-destruct,
wiping out all living beings
except Ancient Gods in the surrounding star system.
Could it be that he mistook the Moonflower
for some kind of treasure ?
If Greed laid his hands on the Moonflower
and he wasn't killed by the Moongazer Serpent,
then he was swallowed by it.
Whatever the Moongazer Serpent swallows
all ends up in the same place.
a few days later
The Moongazer Serpent has its own circulation system.
Excretions don't get expelled
they are instead absorbed again
to make more nutrients
for the body.
Isn't this just a cesspool ?
Is...
Is there a fellow cultivator outside ?
It really is him...
Fellow cultivator !
If you can help this old man to leave this place,
I will
offer you all the artifacts
that I have collected in my life !
Greed has been imprisoned here
but no one has come to save him.
It seems like he came all alone
to the Allheaven Star System.
That's perfect.
With no lingering concerns,
I can safely start extracting the bone.
This gash left by Greed
will actually come in handy.
Extracting the Moongazer Serpent's bone
ranks in the top 3 most dangerous things
I have ever done in my life.
The cultivation path is a journey against fate.
Opportunities come and go in an instant.
Once the Moongazer Serpent fully awakens,
there will not be another chance to extract the bone.
Now or never !
Dao of
the Underworld !
Power of the Underworld !
At the bottom of the Tide Abyss,
I sensed the rift between the two star systems
and understood this spell by chance.
Now, while the Moongazer Serpent is drugged,
I will use that suction force
to extract the Moongazer Serpent's bone.
Extract the bone !
This bone is too big,
It won't fit into a bag of holding.
I must quickly leave before the Moongazer Serpent
wakes up.
Rise !
The Moongazer Serpent is about to wake up.
Celestial Guard !
Restriction Flag
You have followed me for most of my 900 years,
but today...
I must use you to escape danger.
Fall !
Master,
we...
we're falling !
It's the entire continent that's rising...
The Moongazer Serpent is raising its head.
Quick, go !
Just a little more.
If I can delay it for just a moment,
I can escape through these clouds.
These are...
The Seven Stars Sword Formation !
Seven swords, back in formation,
heed my command !
Explode !
You... (Ancient God's language)
dare ! (Ancient God's language)
The Ancient God's language !?
Just a single word
can shatter space.
This is the shattering spell that only 8-stars Ancient Gods can use !
Tu Si's memories didn't show me
that Moongazer Serpents could speak the Ancient God's language !
Withdraw ! (Ancient God's language)
It...
has awakened.
The heavens have not forsaken me,
I'm finally free !
Wang Lin !?
It's you !
I will now
grind your bones to dust !
Since it has come to this,
I'll give you half
of the Moongazer Serpent's bone !
He...
He threw down a mountain ?
Wang Lin, you little thief !
Stop !
Since you've come out,
you can be the decoy to attract the Moongazer Serpent.
No !
Even if I have to burn my lifespan,
I will never go back to that godforsaken place !
Damn it !
I don't want
this cauldron anymore !
You're trying to kill me ?
Not a chance !
The Mountains and Rivers Painting...
Although it's a fake,
its power is truly astonishing.
Moongazer's Wrath
In Tu Si's memories,
If the law of the heavens has a spirit,
then the Ancient Gods have Moongazers.
The Moongazer's Wrath
is like the finger of an Ancient God.
With my current strength,
I have no way to withstand this.
How could there be
a trace of Dao on this fingerprint ?
What kind of spell is this !?
This beast is too strong.
Stop !
Wang Lin !!!
Celestial Emperor Crown
To activate this Celestial Emperor Crown,
I killed 9999 mortal emperors
and fused their souls inside it !
I refuse to believe it won't stop this beast's finger !
Life Seals,
go !
Second Celestial Guard,
Ling Tianhou's sword energy !
Go !
This is bad, this is bad...
We can't win this fight
nor can we run away !
I only have one last way
to get out of this situation !
If I abandon the burden of my physical body,
I can increase my speed
in my Origin Soul form !
1 month later
What the hell is this thing ?
Right now,
I have also exhausted my origin energy.
But the Moongazer Serpent's stamina is endless...
In front of me
is the Southern Domain of Allheaven.
The Moongazer Serpent
has stopped !
Could it be that it's hesitating to leave
the Northern Domain ?
This Moongazer Serpent is astonishingly powerful
yet it's afraid to enter into this place.
Could there be something even more terrifying than it
in the Southern Domain of Allheaven ?
Forget it...
I won't overthink it for now.
After all my preparations,
I never expected this trip to be such a close call.
Right now, I need to find a safe place to go into seclusion
and form a new physical body.
Then, I'll refine this Moongazer Serpent's bone.
The completion of the Heaven Defying Bead
is right before me.
In the memories of Ancient God Tu Si, there was one line he used to describe the Moongazer Serpents.\N“If the law of the heavens has a spirit, then the Ancient Gods have Moongazers!”\NThe spirit can be considered a soul. In short, the first half of the sentence states that the heavens are alive. They have their own existence or a sense of spirit that normal creatures can’t detect.\NThe second half is referring to the Moongazer Serpent. Even Ancient God Tu Si didn’t know how the Moongazer Serpents came to be. They seemed to have already existed for a very long time. It was like the heavens and their spirit, both were elusive things that no one could explain.\N\NYou might wonder how Wang Lin was able to use his Life Seals after he had extracted them previously. He had stored his Life Seals inside his Celestial Guard for it to use them. They just can't regenerate anymore.\N\NWang Lin almost lost his wits. This finger was too fast, and it was quickly closing in. In the midst of this crisis, Wang Lin’s eyes became cold and he placed his hand on the celestial guard. He extracted the slaughter energy from the celestial guard. In an instant, almost one million strands of slaughter energy appeared. They transformed into life seals to block the ancient god finger!\NThe life seals all collapsed as if they were fragile pieces of paper. It didn’t matter how much slaughter energy was used, all of it was powerless before the ancient god finger.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.